Guide to the Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 2
Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 2
- Box: 73, folder: 8 (Box 73, Folder 8)
  - Item 15: Comparative Headcount By Employment Information Centers, Publication (Box 73, Folder 8)
  - Item 16: Comparative Headcount by Employment Information Centers, Publication (Box 73, Folder 8)
  - Item 17: Comparison of 1966 and 1965 Daily Hirings by Areas in the Port of New York, Publication (Box 73, Folder 8)
  - Item 18: August Pier Employment Shows 10% Increase in Port of New York to Reverse Trend, Publication (Box 73, Folder 8)
    By Waterfront Commission of NY Harbor. September 14, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 19: News Release, Publication (Box 73, Folder 8)
    By Waterfront Commission of NY Harbor. April 16, 1971. Item is in English.
  - Item 20: News Release, Publication (Box 73, Folder 8)
    By Waterfront Commission of NY Harbor. November 10, 1970. Item is in English.
  - Item 21: News Release, Publication (Box 73, Folder 8)
    By Waterfront Commission of NY Harbor. December 16, 1970. Item is in English.
  - Item 22: Holiday Message, Publication (Box 73, Folder 8)
  - Item 23: News Release, Publication (Box 73, Folder 8)
    By Waterfront Commission of NY Harbor. August 20, 1970. Item is in English.
  - Item 24: News Release, Publication (Box 73, Folder 8)
    By Waterfront Commission of NY Harbor. July 15, 1970. Item is in English.
  - Item 25: News Release, Publication (Box 73, Folder 8)
    By Waterfront Commission of NY Harbor. August 12, 1970. Item is in English.
  - Item 26: News Release, Publication (Box 73, Folder 8)
    By Waterfront Commission of NY Harbor. September 10, 1970. Item is in English.
  - Item 27: Waterfront Commission Imposes $66,000 Fine, Publication (Box 73, Folder 8)
    By Waterfront Commission of NY Harbor. May 2, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 28: Piers Agency ContinuesIts Watchdog Role on Waterfront, Publication (Box 73, Folder 8)
    By Waterfront Commission of NY Harbor. May 15, 1968. Item is in English.
- Box: 73, folder: 9 (Box 73, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Hiring Practices for Longshoremen, Publication (Box 73, Folder 9)
    By Phyllis Groom. November 1965. Item is in English.
- Box: 73, folder: 10 (Box 73, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Waterfront Commission Tells Governors and Legislators New York Port Benefits from Improvement in Conditions, Publication (Box 73, Folder 10)
    By Waterfront Commission of New York. March 20, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Interim Report on Current Work Stoppage, Publication (Box 73, Folder 10)
    By Waterfront Commission of New York Harbor. March 25, 1954. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Notice to the International Longshorement Assoc., New York Shipping Assoc., and Employers of Registered Longshore Labor, Publication (Box 73, Folder 10)
    By Waterfront Commission of New York Harbor. January 12, 1955. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Memorandum Filed with Assembly Bill, Introductory Number 9, Publication (Box 73, Folder 10)
    By Waterfront Commission of New York Harbor. June 30, 1953. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Summary of an Act, Publication (Box 73, Folder 10)
  - Item 6: In Assembly Extraordinary Session- June 26, 1953, Publication (Box 73, Folder 10)
    By Waterfront Commission of New York Harbor. June 26, 1953. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: In Assembly Extraordinary Session- June 26, 1953, Publication (Box 73, Folder 10)
    By Waterfront Commission of New York Harbor. June 26, 1953, copy 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: In Assembly Extraordinary Session- June 25, 1953, Publication (Box 73, Folder 10)
    By Waterfront Commission of New York Harbor. June 25, 1953. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: In Assembly Extraordinary Session- June 25, 1953, Publication (Box 73, Folder 10)
    By Waterfront Commission of New York Harbor. June 25, 1953, copy 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: In Assembly Extraordinary Session- June 25, 1953, Publication (Box 73, Folder 10)
    By Waterfront Commission of New York Harbor. June 25, 1953, copy 3. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: Memorandum Filed with Assembly Bill, Introductory Number 9, Publication (Box 73, Folder 10)
    By Waterfront Commission of New York Harbor. June 30, 1953; copy 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: Extraordinary Session, Publication (Box 73, Folder 10)
    By The Legislative Index Company. June 25, 1953. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: Second Extraordinary Session, Publication (Box 73, Folder 10)
    By The Legislative Index Company. Novembe 17, 1953. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: Extraordinary Session, Publication (Box 73, Folder 10)
    By The Legislative Index Company. June 18, 1953. Item is in English.
  - Item 15: Second Extraordinary Session: Bill Introduced and Action Taken in Senate, Publication (Box 73, Folder 10)
    By The Legislative Index Company. November 18, 1953. Item is in English.
- Box: 73, folder: 11 (Box 73, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Wanamaker Deal with Union Gains- Loose Clippings, Publication (Box 73, Folder 11)
    By New York Times. November 5, 1954. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Union Bid Vetoed by Wanamakers- Loose Clippings, Publication (Box 73, Folder 11)
    By New York Times. November 18, 1954. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Wanamaker Sale to Union Proposed- Loose Clippings, Publication (Box 73, Folder 11)
    By New York Times. October 27, 1954. Item is in English.
- Box: 73, folder: 12 (Box 73, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Interim Report on Current Work Stoppage, Publication (Box 73, Folder 12)
  - Item 2: Interim Report on Current Work Stoppage, Publication (Box 73, Folder 12)
    By Waterfront Commission of New York Harbor. March 25, 1954; copy 2. Item is in English.
- Box: 73, folder: 13 (Box 73, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Constitution of the Labor Historians and Letter to Members, Publication (Box 73, Folder 13)
    By Wayne State University. Item is in English.
- Box: 73, folder: 14 (Box 73, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: The Labor Historians Newsletter, Publication (Box 73, Folder 14)
    By Wayne State University. Spring, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: The Labor Historians Newsletter, Publication (Box 73, Folder 14)
    By Wayne State University. Spring 1968; copy. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: The Labor Historians Newsletter, Publication (Box 73, Folder 14)
    By Wayne State University. Fall 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: The Labor Historians Newsletter, Publication (Box 73, Folder 14)
    By Wayne State University. Fall 1967; copy. Item is in English.
- Box: 73, folder: 15 (Box 73, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: Agreement Between Weirton Steel Company and Weirton Independent Union, Publication (Box 73, Folder 15)
    By Weirton Steel Company. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: HOLCO, Publication (Box 73, Folder 15)
  - Item 3: Supplemental Agreement (Retirement Pay Program), Publication (Box 73, Folder 15)
  - Item 4: Agreement Between Weirten Steel Company and Weirton Independent Union, Inc., Publication (Box 73, Folder 15)
    By Weirton Steel Company. November 22, 1949. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Agreement Between Weirton Steel Company and Independent Steelworkers Union, Publication (Box 73, Folder 15)
    By Weirton Steel Company. July 1, 1954. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Agreement Between Weirton Steel Company and Independent Steelworkers Union, Publication (Box 73, Folder 15)
    By Weirton Steel Company. June 24, 1952. Item is in English.
- Box: 73, folder: 16 (Box 73, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: Souvenir Program Dedication Ceremonies at Weirton Community Center, Publication (Box 73, Folder 16)
    By Weirton Steel Company. March 1-4, 1952. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: A Commentary on Current Events, Publication (Box 73, Folder 16)
  - Item 3: Ideas for Improvement, Publication (Box 73, Folder 16)
- Box: 73, folder: 17 (Box 73, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: Weirton, West Virginia: The Steel Center of the Mountain State, Publication (Box 73, Folder 17)
    By Weirton Steel Company. November 1963. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Weirton Steel Company, Publication (Box 73, Folder 17)
    By T.J. Ess. 2 articles, one of which was reprinted from the "Iron and Steel Engineer" issue, the other reprinted from the "Steubenville Herald Star"; November 1958. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Notes on the Foreign Situation Based on a Trip Abroad, Publication (Box 73, Folder 17)
    By Ernest T. Weir. June 19, 1953; Grant Building. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: What's Behind High Prices?, Publication (Box 73, Folder 17)
  - Item 5: Lessons of the Steel Strike, Publication (Box 73, Folder 17)
    By Dr. Leo Wolman. Repreinted from "The Freeman"; letter from Ernest T. Weir attached introducing the article. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: The Mighty Tin Can, Publication (Box 73, Folder 17)
    By Edward Toledano. Reprinted from the Weirton Steel Employee Bulletin. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Weirton-- Where Freedom Rings, Publication (Box 73, Folder 17)
    By William A. White. Reprinted from The Pittsburgh Press; September 22-29, 1951. Item is in English.
- Box: 73, folder: 18 (Box 73, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: Personnel Inventory, Publication (Box 73, Folder 18)
  - Item 2: Cost Improvement Through Improved Methods, Publication (Box 73, Folder 18)
    By Weirton Steel Company. March 16, 1964. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Application for Employment, Publication (Box 73, Folder 18)
  - Item 4: Weirton Offers You More Than a Job- There's a Future For You in Steel, Publication (Box 73, Folder 18)
    By Weirton Steel Company. October 1964. Item is in English.
- Box: 73, folder: 19 (Box 73, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: Welch's Grapevine, Publication (Box 73, Folder 19)
    By Welch Grape Juice Company, Inc. February 1956. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: preparing Your Vocational Guidance talk for a High School Class, Publication (Box 73, Folder 19)
    By The Welch Grape Juice Company, Inc. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: 1965 Annual Report, Publication (Box 73, Folder 19)
- Box: 73, folder: 20 (Box 73, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: Welch's, Publication (Box 73, Folder 20)
  - Item 2: The Welch Point of View, Publication (Box 73, Folder 20)
    By The Welch Grape Juice Company, Inc. July 1956. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Westfield Fact Sheet, Publication (Box 73, Folder 20)
  - Item 4: The Welch Point-of-View: A Statement of Employee Relations Principles, Publication (Box 73, Folder 20)
    By The Welch Grape Juice Company, Inc. September 15, 1965. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: The Welch Way: A Secretarial Handbook for use by Welch and National Personnel, Publication (Box 73, Folder 20)
- Box: 73, folder: 21 (Box 73, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: How Wesley Hospital Developed Its Own Personnel Policies and Practices Manual, Publication (Box 73, Folder 21)
    By Wesley Hospital. February 1, 1960. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: What's Your Idea?, Publication (Box 73, Folder 21)
    By Western Electric Company. Employee suggestion system guide. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: What's Your Idea?, Publication (Box 73, Folder 21)
    By Western Electric Company. different employee suggestion guide. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: What's Your Idea?, Publication (Box 73, Folder 21)
    By Western Electric Company. different employee suggestion guide; copy. Item is in English.
- Box: 73, folder: 22 (Box 73, Folder 22)
  - Item 1: News Article on WESTAR, Publication (Box 73, Folder 22)
    By Western Union Corporation. June 25, 1974. Item is in English.
- Box: 73, folder: 23 (Box 73, Folder 23)
  - Item 1: News Article on WESTAR, Publication (Box 73, Folder 23)
    By Western Union Corporation. May 14, 1974. Item is in English.
- Box: 73, folder: 24 (Box 73, Folder 24)
  - Item 1: Guilford Center Surpasses United Way Goal for 1977, Publication (Box 73, Folder 24)
    By Western Electric Company. News Special Focus; October 13, 1977. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Newsline Article, Publication (Box 73, Folder 24)
    By Western Electric Company. October 17, 1977. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Court Denies AT&T Petition, Publication (Box 73, Folder 24)
    By Western Electric Company. News briefs article; October 5, 1977. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Debutts, Hough Testify Before Congressional Subcommittees, Publication (Box 73, Folder 24)
    By Western Electric Company. March 28, 1977. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Amplifier Newsletter, Publication (Box 73, Folder 24)
    By Western Electric Company. July/August 1977 issue. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: "Guilford Center Focus" Newsletter, Publication (Box 73, Folder 24)
    By Western Electric Company. September 1977 issue. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Western Electric Magazine, Publication (Box 73, Folder 24)
    By Western Electric Company. May-June 1977 issue; "No Job is So Important and No Service is so Urgent That We Cannot Take Time to Perform Our Work Safely". Item is in English.
- Box: 73, folder: 25 (Box 73, Folder 25)
  - Item 1: Westinghouse News, Publication (Box 73, Folder 25)
    By Westinghouse Electric Corporation. volume 33, number 3; March 1978. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Management Organization Chart, Publication (Box 73, Folder 25)
    By Westinghouse Electric Corporation. June 1977. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Westinghouse Gateway News, Publication (Box 73, Folder 25)
    By Westinghouse Electric Corporation. February 1978. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Westinghouse News Bulletin, Publication (Box 73, Folder 25)
    By Westinghouse Electric Corporation. February 1975. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Westinghouse News Bulletin, Publication (Box 73, Folder 25)
    By Westinghouse Electric Corporation. January 1975. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Westinghouse News, Publication (Box 73, Folder 25)
  - Item 7: Westinghouse News, Publication (Box 73, Folder 25)
    By Westinghouse Electric Corporation. February 1975; copy. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Large Power Tranformer Division News, Publication (Box 73, Folder 25)
    By Westinghouse Electric Corporation. March 7, 1975. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Management Briefs, Publication (Box 73, Folder 25)
- Box: 73, folder: 26 (Box 73, Folder 26)
  - Item 1: The Record of 1959 and What It Meant to Westinghouse Employes, Publication (Box 73, Folder 26)
    By Westinghouse Electric Company. Westinghouse news annual report issue. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Westinghouse Sound Films, Publication (Box 73, Folder 26)
    By Westinghouse Electric Company. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Westinghouse News: Tube Topics, Publication (Box 73, Folder 26)
    By Westinghouse Electric Company. vol. 5; August 1958. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Westinghouse News: Home Edition, Publication (Box 73, Folder 26)
    By Westinghouse Electric Company. vol. 13, no. 9; September 1958. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Westinghouse at East Pittsburgh, Publication (Box 73, Folder 26)
    By Westinghouse Electric Corporation. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: 1957 Annual Report, Publication (Box 73, Folder 26)
  - Item 7: Westinghouse News: 12 Divisions Honored for Serving Customers, Publication (Box 73, Folder 26)
    By Westinghouse Electric Corporation. May 1967; Vol. 22, no. 5. Item is in English.
- Box: 73, folder: 27 (Box 73, Folder 27)
  - Item 1: This Is Westinghouse, Publication (Box 73, Folder 27)
  - Item 2: Improving Costs with an Active Suggestion Program, Publication (Box 73, Folder 27)
  - Item 3: Westinghouse Program Documents and Forms, Publication (Box 73, Folder 27)
    By Westinghouse Electric Corporation. May 21, 1970. Item is in English.
- Box: 73, folder: 28 (Box 73, Folder 28)
  - Item 1: Westinghouse Fires Undesirable Employees, Publication (Box 73, Folder 28)
  - Item 2: Our Secretary, Miss Jones, Publication (Box 73, Folder 28)
    By Nadine Hail. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: The Westinghouse Report for 1955, Publication (Box 73, Folder 28)
  - Item 4: Big Things are Happening at Westinghouse, Publication (Box 73, Folder 28)
  - Item 5: Automation Adds to Employment, Publication (Box 73, Folder 28)
    By Westinghouse Electric Corporation. vol. 10, no. 14; July 5, 1955. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Plant Police Have Many Responsibilities, Publication (Box 73, Folder 28)
    By Westinghouse Electric Corporation. vol. 2, no. 4; April 10, 1956. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Westinghouse News: Watch Westinghouse!, Publication (Box 73, Folder 28)
    By Westinghouse Electric Company. April 12, 1956. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Westinghouse Annual Report 1955, Publication (Box 73, Folder 28)
  - Item 9: Westinghouse Invitation, Publication (Box 73, Folder 28)
  - Item 10: Improving Costs with an Active Suggestion Program, Publication (Box 73, Folder 28)
  - Item 11: Westinghouse 1966 Suggestion Report, Publication (Box 73, Folder 28)
    By Westinghouse Electric Company. May 3, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: IRRA newsletter, Publication (Box 73, Folder 28)
    By Industrial Relations Research Association. Summer, 1970; vol. 8 no. 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: Management Organization, Publication (Box 73, Folder 28)
    By Westinghouse Electric Corporation. employee chart. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: Nine Urban Problems and Some Solutions From Westinghouse, Publication (Box 73, Folder 28)
  - Item 15: Management Newsletter- Food for Thought, Publication (Box 73, Folder 28)
    By Westinghouse Electric Corporation. July 28, 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 16: Management Newsletter, Publication (Box 73, Folder 28)
    By Westinghouse Electric Corporation. July 21, 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 17: Aerospace News Bulletins, Publication (Box 73, Folder 28)
    By Westinghouse Electric Corporation. December 8, 1969 and November 19, 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 18: R&D Newsletter, Publication (Box 73, Folder 28)
    By Westinghouse Electric Corporation. March 31, 1970; vol. 5, no. 13. Item is in English.
  - Item 19: 1966 Annual Report, Publication (Box 73, Folder 28)
  - Item 20: Westinghouse 1969 Suggestion Report, Publication (Box 73, Folder 28)
    By Westinghouse Electric Corporation. March 23, 1970. Item is in English.
  - Item 21: Westinghouse 1968 Suggestion Report, Publication (Box 73, Folder 28)
    By Westinghouse Electric Corporation. May 9, 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 22: The Record of 1952, Publication (Box 73, Folder 28)
- Box: 73, folder: 29 (Box 73, Folder 29)
  - Item 1: Westinghouse News, Publication (Box 73, Folder 29)
  - Item 2: Employe Relations in Perspective, Publication (Box 73, Folder 29)
    By Westinghouse Electric Corporation. A Talk by Howard S. Kaltenborn; June 8, 1960. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Constitution of the Association of Westinghouse Engineers, Publication (Box 73, Folder 29)
    By Westinghouse Electric Corporation. January 14, 1958. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Management Guide: Disciplinary Action- Illegal Work Stoppages, Publication (Box 73, Folder 29)
    By Westinghouse Electric Corporation. September 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Regulations of the Westinghouse Electric & Manufacturing Corporation Relief Department, Publication (Box 73, Folder 29)
    By Westinghouse Electric Corporation. January 1915. Item is in English.
- Box: 73, folder: 30 (Box 73, Folder 30)
  - Item 1: Working with Westinghouse at the Raleigh Meter Plant, Publication (Box 73, Folder 30)
  - Item 2: Tact, Publication (Box 73, Folder 30)
    By Sir John Lubbock. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Announcement of the Plan of the Westinghouse Electric & Manufacturing Company for Employees", Publication (Box 73, Folder 30)
    By Westinghouse Electric Corporation. December 1914. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Westinghouse Welcomes, Publication (Box 73, Folder 30)
  - Item 5: Welcome to Westinghouse, Publication (Box 73, Folder 30)
  - Item 6: Finding Your Place in Industry, Publication (Box 73, Folder 30)
  - Item 7: Reassignment Certification, Publication (Box 73, Folder 30)
  - Item 8: 1955 Diary and Employee Handbook, Publication (Box 73, Folder 30)
  - Item 9: Management Guide- Internal Communications, Publication (Box 73, Folder 30)
    By Westinghouse Electric Corporation. October 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: Management Guide- Equal Employment Opportunity, Publication (Box 73, Folder 30)
  - Item 11: Personnel Procedures Sheet, Publication (Box 73, Folder 30)
  - Item 12: Personnel Procedures Packet, Publication (Box 73, Folder 30)
- Box: 73, folder: 31 (Box 73, Folder 31)
  - Item 1: Rules for Promoting Safety in Testing Operations, Publication (Box 73, Folder 31)
  - Item 2: Rules and Safe Practices for Industrial Truck Operations, Publication (Box 73, Folder 31)
  - Item 3: How One Westinghouse Plant Set an All-Time Safety Record for the Electrical Industry, Publication (Box 73, Folder 31)
    By Westinghouse Electric Corporation. "It's an Idea" from Dartnell. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Achievements Because of Cooperation, Publication (Box 73, Folder 31)
  - Item 5: Accident Prevention- Facts and Figures for 1953, Publication (Box 73, Folder 31)
    By Westinghouse Electric Corporation. Facts and Figures for 1953. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Your Copy of Accident Precention Facts and Figures for Fifty Four, Publication (Box 73, Folder 31)
  - Item 7: Safety Rules for the Operation & Repair of Cranes, Portable Ladders, Elevators, Industrial Trucks, Publication (Box 73, Folder 31)
    By Westinghouse Electric Corporation. revised January 1946. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Six Steps to a New Safety Peak, Publication (Box 73, Folder 31)
    By Westinghouse Electric Corporation. November 1957. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Safety Information Letter, Publication (Box 73, Folder 31)
    By Westinghouse Electric Corporation. August 25, 1955. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: A Guide for Your Safety, Publication (Box 73, Folder 31)
- Box: 74, folder: 1 (Box 74, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Continued Education- Announcement of Courses, Publication (Box 74, Folder 1)
    By Business and Management Program. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Continued Education for Westinghouse Professional Personnel, Publication (Box 74, Folder 1)
    By Westinghouse Training and Development Department. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Westinghouse Pension Plan, Publication (Box 74, Folder 1)
    By Westinghouse Electric Corp. Jan. 1, 1951. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Facts About Unemployment Compensation for the Guidance of Supervisors, Publication (Box 74, Folder 1)
    By Westinghouse Electric Corp. Decembr 1953. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Westinghouse Insurance Plan for Employes, Publication (Box 74, Folder 1)
    By Westinghouse Electric Corp. effective December 1, 1955. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Management Disability Benefits Program, Publication (Box 74, Folder 1)
    By Westinghouse Electric Corp. effective September 1, 1965. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Questions and Answers about the Westinghouse Personal Savings and Personal Investment Plans, Publication (Box 74, Folder 1)
    By Westinghouse Electric Corp. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Westinghouse Personal Savings Plan, Publication (Box 74, Folder 1)
  - Item 9: Westinghouse Insurance and Pension Plan, Publication (Box 74, Folder 1)
  - Item 10: Westinghouse Personal Investment Plan, Publication (Box 74, Folder 1)
  - Item 11: Westinghouse Insurance and Pension Plan, Publication (Box 74, Folder 1)
    By Westinghouse Electric Corp. copy 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: Westinghouse Pension Plan, Publication (Box 74, Folder 1)
    By Westinghouse Electric Corp. effective Jan. 1, 1951. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: Moving Expenses for Transferred Employes- Management Guide, Publication (Box 74, Folder 1)
    By Westinghouse Electric Corp. April 1970. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: Technical Paper, Publication (Box 74, Folder 1)
    By United Steel Corp. Fall 1959. Item is in English.